<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-rsses on UnContainer</title>
    <link>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-rsses on UnContainer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.uncontainer.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Containers</title>
      <link>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We at Uncontainer, allow you to cleanly separate what has traditionally has been dumped on a single big server (which you can still use).
Everything is concise, easy-to-understand, and easily replace-able components.
For example, with Docker, it’s easy to swap out your Apache container for your nginx container in a way that doesn’t affect your application because it can run fine with any of your web server containers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We built a platform for an innovative lending platform based on Docker which abstracted out redis, elasticsearch, postgresql, ruby on rails and celery.
This platform was migrated from Rackspace -&amp;gt; AWS within a few hours as a consequence of containerization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/second/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes allows you to compose your complicated infrastructure as a interconnected set of containers. You can scale this from 1 to thousands of containers (all with their own complex set of dependencies).
Watch how Monzo is doing this at scale in &lt;a href=&#34;//www.youtube.com/watch?v=YkOY7DgXKyw&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Building a bank with Kubernetes at Monzo&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud compatible!</title>
      <link>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.uncontainer.com/post/third/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Docker and Kubernetes are compatible with various cloud providers - including Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud and Microsoft Azure&amp;hellip;. as well as bare metal, plain servers like Rackspace and Softlayer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>